Today we have Sheikh Abu Yad with us, he will tell us the details
and on our nature, they will show us the right light that we pray in, by the will of Allah
In the name of God, the Most Gracious, the Most Merciful. Peace and blessings be upon the Messenger
First, there should be a desire. Any work should have a desire.
We don't separate people and their needs
But the questions are as the Prophet, peace be upon him, said:
Wash your hands.
I will try to remove the water from the fish
I have to say that the water is not enough to boil the fish.
and the same for the honeycomb, you can use a stick or a stick and you can do it yourself
but we will always keep the water in the bowl
and put it in the oven.
3 times then I wash my face 3 times
and from the scalp to the bottom of the head
The water is boiling
if you have a beard, let it be, there is no beard
then cut the chicken, it should be always on the right side
I washed my hair not from here to here, but from here to here
here we blow from the first part of the fingers to the end of the nose three times
then left from the first to the end
I start from here to here 3 times with the help of a spoon
The more difficult, the more difficult, and then they get lost, and in the end you come to a dry place
because the whole place is changed. Then, I wipe the head. I wipe the head, and I leave the head for the head.
one ear and two sides and with the same water in the ears
Then we go to the feet, there is no neck, there is no such thing. We go to the feet, in the name of God
Three times, look, put your fingers in, one, and see how your legs are.
The hands should be on the whole leg
3 2 and 1
Now we add the onions
and then we add the salt
like this, make sure that everything is well-soaked
then we will cut the meat and put it in the oven
There is no company, and I think that Muhammad is worshiping his messenger.
God made me from the repentant and made me from the purified. Peace be upon you all.